hook.tv 2007-12-03

# Hook.tv: Flyfishing

## Hook.tv Privacy Policy

Hook.tv is committed to protecting your privacy. By using the Hook.tv website (www.hook.tv) or downloading the Hook.tv Media Center software and registering as a user, you are consenting to the collection and use of information by Hook.tv in conformance with the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the Hook.tv Privacy Policy, please do not register with any Hook.tv product. This document was last updated February 12, 2007. Information Collection and Use We will only use the information we collect for the purposes of providing you with a more personalized experience. Hook.tv is the sole owner of the information collected and we do not share the information unless specifically stated otherwise within this policy. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to other parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users during registration and when you make updates to your personal information in the Tools section of the Hook.tv Media Center. In order to ensure the integrity of your personal information, all of your data is stored in secure Hook.tv server databases.

### Hook.tv Registration

When you choose to view, purchase, or download media files from Hook.tv, you will be required to register as a Hook.tv user. Registering allows you to take advantage of our unique, personalized features and services. Upon registering, you will first be asked to provide your e-mail address, a unique username, a password, name, gender, and date of birth. For billing information we will collect the type of credit card, your name as it appears on your credit card, credit card number, CVN (if applicable), expiration date, billing address, city, state, and zip code. You may also elect to provide us with your areas of interest.

This information is collected for personal identification, billing authorization, and to further personalize your Hook.tv experience. Information is stored on secure Hook.tv servers. All information collected allows you access to your account information and various Hook.tv features.

This information also allows us to comply to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) ensuring that registered users of Hook.tv are 13 years of age or older. If a prospective user attempts to register and indicates that they are under the age of 13, we will not allow such registration to continue and will delete all information relating to such prospective user other than the name and email address for purposes of cross referencing any future attempts to register as a user with information relating to the age of the prospective user that may be different from the age set forth in the original registration.

### Newsletters

As a Hook.tv user, you may choose to occasionally receive e-mail updates from us or our partners, including newsletters, special offers we think you will find valuable, feature enhancements, and new services. These e-mail updates and offers may be sent based on information you have provided including previous purchases and downloads. Please note that by electing to receive e-mail updates from our partners, you are electing to have your information shared with these partners. For information on unsubscribing to Hook.tv or Hook.tv partner newsletters, please see the Opt Out Section below.

### Contests and Promotions

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your username, name, address, phone number, date of birth, or e-mail address so that we can administer the contest and notify winners. Additionally, you may be able to choose whether you would like to receive further communications from Hook.tv Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Promotions that are offered through our website may be sponsored by companies other than Hook.tv or may be co-sponsored by Hook.tv and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data is shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. Participation in these promotions is completely voluntary, and you can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared.

### Online Surveys

We value opinions and comments from our users, and you may have the opportunity to give us your feedback through online surveys. In conducting these surveys, we may ask for your name, username, address, or e-mail address so that we can appropriately identify you. Survey information collected will be aggregated and used to improve our services and general offerings. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

### Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID the site uses to recognize you. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. The only personal information a cookie contains is the information you provide yourself. The Hook.tv Media Center does not use "Cookies", but "Cookies" may be used when you use Hook.tv Website or connect to an advertisers Website. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can set your browser to block them in the future. This action, however, may result in a less personalized experience with Hook.tv and other websites. When you enter personal information on Hook.tv software, its website, or with a third party by means of advertising and you have elected to accept cookies, your personally identifiable information will be linked to a cookie on your computer. Hook.tv does not control the policies and practices of its advertisers. You are therefore advised to contact such advertisers directly with any questions you may have concerning their privacy or other policies or practices.

### Log Files

The Hook.tv software and other Hook.tv technologies create log files identifying the media files you have purchased, downloaded, played, the number of times they have been played, the last date they were played, and tracking of user activity within our Media Guide. This information is stored in Hook.tv’s secure database and is used for purposes of more readily issuing licenses for media files that you have already downloaded and thereby improving the speed with which you may use such media files in the future. This information is also used to analyze trends, administer the applications and website, diagnose problems, fulfill royalty reporting requirements for acquired media, to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and deliver a personalized user experience within the Media Guide. No personally identifiable information concerning such usage is shared with any other party. Also note certain media players, such as the Microsoft Windows Media Player, may create log files identifying the media files that you have played. Hook.tv does not control the policies and practices of companies offering media players. You are therefore advised to contact such companies directly with any questions you may have concerning their privacy or other policies or practices.

### Sharing Information

When you become a user of Hook.tv’s Services, we may elect to share aggregate demographic or behavioral information with our business partners such as content providers and advertisers. By selecting to receive e-mail from Hook.tv partners, you are also electing to share your personally identifiable information with Hook.tv partners. As a result, Hook.tv may choose to provide your information to a variety of Hook.tv business partners. If you have not elected to share your personally identifiable information with our partners, we will not provide this information to our partners or any other third parties. Hook.tv partners with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

Hook.tv may also disclose information in special cases to the extent it reasonably believes that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Hook.tv’s Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interfering with Hook.tv’s rights or property, other Hook.tv users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Hook.tv will also disclose or access information to the extent it reasonably believes that the law requires it to do so. Hook.tv may also transfer information it collects, including any personally identifiable information, in the course of a sale of all or most of the assets of the company.

### Security

Hook.tv takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information, your information is protected both on- and off-line. However, you should keep in mind that any information that you disclose while on-line might be intercepted and misused by unintended third party recipients.

When Hook.tv uses sensitive information such as a credit card number during an e-commerce transaction, that information is encrypted and protected with industry-standard encryption software Secure Socket Layers (SSL). We have also obtained a digital certificate from GeoTrust Inc., a leading provider of Internet trust services. When you enter a secure portion of the (such as the shopping cart) which contains any of your personal information, the GEOTrust Logo will appear on the page. If you click on this image, a small popup window displaying site-security information will appear. This certificate guarantees that your personal information is being transmitted in secure (encrypted) form to a Hook.tv web server, not to some unknown or unauthorized server.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All information you provide to Hook.tv online is stored on a secure Hook.tv’s server databases. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a highly secure data center behind a series of limited-access locked doors. Access to all of our users’ information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added or new employees are hired, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected.

Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password you created when you registered an account with the (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Associate or any other representative of Hook.tv will ever ask you for your password. So if you receive any correspondence purportedly coming from us, please do not supply any password in response to any such request. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by going to the My Account section of Tools that is part of the application.

If you have any questions about security, please send an e-mail to support@hook.tv

### Special Offers

We send all new members confirmation/welcoming e-mail. Established subscribers who have opted in to receive e-mail on an ongoing basis will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our opt-out below.

### Service Updates

On occasion, we may also send you service announcement updates. Hook.tv users are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with you to provide requested services and issues relating to your account via e-mail or phone.

### Correcting Personal Information

If your personal information changes, or you find that it is inaccurate, you may revise your personal information at any time by signing in using your username and password and going to the Tools section of the Hook.tv Media Center .

### Opt Out

By using the Hook.tv products; you consent to the collection and use of information by Hook.tv in conformance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the Hook.tv Privacy Policy, please do not use or register with Hook.tv products.

Hook.tv users are given the opportunity to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our products (i.e., partner communications) at the point where we ask for that information.

You may, at any time, decline to receive these e-mail notifications from Hook.tv or our affiliated business partners by logging into the Hook.tv Media Center with your username and password, and going to the Tools section or by replying to any e-mail with 'REMOVE' in the subject line.

Users of the Hook.tv products are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require the disclosure of information to an outside party.

### Notification of Changes

Hook.tv reserves the right, at its discretion, to change its Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post notice of a Privacy Policy update on our website so that our users may view our updated policy and be aware on an ongoing basis of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.

### Canceling Your Hook.tv Service

At any point, you may elect to cancel your Hook.tv service. To do so, contact us via email at support@hook.tv.

### Contacting Hook.tv

If you have any questions about this privacy policy statement you can e-mail us at support@hook.tv
